Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society vertical files ARC.315
Brooklyn Historical Society
Brooklyn Historical Society vertical files
1780-2018
Brooklyn Historical Society
Brooklyn Historical Society (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.)
ARC.315
18 Linear Feet in 9 filing cabinet drawers
The Brooklyn Historical Society vertical files is an artificial collection compiled by Brooklyn Historical Society staff, that continues to be updated to the present day. The collection contains pamphlets, cards, advertisements, newspaper articles, magazines, letters, and more dating from 1770 to the present documenting Brooklyn, New York City, and Long Island. This collection also includes biographical files on notable Brooklyn individuals.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Brooklyn Historical Society vertical files is an artificial collection compiled by the Brooklyn Historical Society staff, that continues to be updated to the present day.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series: Series 1. New York City and Long Island, Series 2. Brooklyn, Series 3. Biographical.
Series 1 and 2 are arranged alphabetically by topic, while Series 3 is organized alphabetically by last name.
Biographical / Historical
The Brooklyn Historical Society vertical files is an artificial collection compiled by Brooklyn Historical Society staff, that continues to be updated to the present day.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains pamphlets, cards, advertisements, newspaper articles, magazines, letters, and more dating from 1770 to the present. The first series documents life in New York City and Long Island, including individual communities, organizations, and events. This series includes materials on counties and boroughs such as Queens, Staten Island, and Suffolk County. The second series documents life in Brooklyn through files on individual neighborhoods, landscapes, organizations, events, local government, and businesses. The third series documents individuals from Brooklyn and Brooklyn-based families. Notable individuals represented in this collection include Walt Whitman, Henry Ward Beecher, Gabriel Furman, Jackie Robinson, and members of the Roebling and Shellens families. This collection also includes information about lesser known organizations and individuals.
African Americans; Baseball |z New York (State) |z New York; Historic preservation |z New York (State) |z New York; Museums |z New York (State) | New York; Museums |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Parks |z New York (State) |z New York; Public schools |z New York (State) |z New York; Abolitionists |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Banks and banking |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Historic buildings |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Charities |z New York (State) |z New York; City churches |z New York (State) |z Kings County; African American churches |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Political clubs |z New York (State) |z New York; Food -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Hospitals |x Medical staff |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Labor |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Neighborhoods |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Nonprofit organizations |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Universities and colleges |z New York (State) |z Kings County |x History; Theater |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Transportation |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Kings County (N.Y.) |x Genealogy; Staten Island (New York, N.Y.); Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.); Artists |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Gay culture |z New York (State) |z New York; Manhattan (New York, N.Y.); Suffolk County (N.Y.); Long Island (N.Y.); Queens County (N.Y.)
- Series 1: New York City and Long Island, 1850-2018; 2 Linear Feet in 1 filing cabinet drawer
  - African Americans, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Art and Artists, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Baseball -- General, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Baseball -- Yankees, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Bicentennial, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Bridges, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Business and Businesses -- General, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Business and Businesses -- Long Island Lighting Company (LILCO), undated (Drawer 1)
  - Buildings, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Churches, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Cemetaries, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Disasters, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Environment -- General, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Environment -- Long Island Sound Studies, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Health -- Birth Control Clinics, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Health -- Sanger, Margaret, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Historic Preservation -- Committee for the Preservation of…, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Historic Preservation -- Friends of Cast Iron Architecture, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Historic Preservation -- Landmarks, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Historic Preservation -- National Trust for Historic Preservation, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Historic Preservation -- Preservation League of New York State, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Historic Preservation -- Society for the Preservation of Long Island, undated (Drawer 1)
  - History, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Holidays, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Housing, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Libraries, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Babylon, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Dix Hills, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- East Hampton, L.I., undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Old Beth Page, L.I., undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Oyster Bay, L.I., undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Port Jefferson, L.I., undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Queens Village, L.I., undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Roslyn, L.I., undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Sag Harbor, L.I., undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Southampton, L.I., undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Suffolk County, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Long Island--Communities-- Water Mill, L.I., undated (Drawer 1)
  - Maritime, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Monuments and Statues, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- General, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- American Museum of Natural History, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- Castle Clinton National Monument, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- Museum of the City of New York, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- Nassau County Museums, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- Queens Historical Society, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- Queens Museum, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- Sleepy Hollow Restoration, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- South Street Seaport Museum, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- Studio Museum in Harlem, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- Suffolk County Marine Museum, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- University Art Gallery of the University State, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Museums -- Whaling Museum, Cold Spring Harbor, L..I., undated (Drawer 1)
  - New Jersey, undated (Drawer 1)
  - New York City, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Organizations -- Center for Social Inclusion, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Organizations -- League of Women Voters, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Organizations -- Queens Botanical Garden Society, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Parks -- General, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Parks -- Central Park, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Parks -- Battery Park and Battery Park Basin, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Parks -- Flushing Meadow Park, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Parks -- Gateway National Recreation Area, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Parks -- Rochdale Village Park, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Politics, Government, Legal, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Queens, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Religion, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Sciences, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Schools -- General, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Schools -- Columbia University, undated (Drawer 1)
  - Staten Island, N.Y., undated (Drawer 2)
  - Tourism and City Guides, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Transportation, undated (Drawer 2)
  - World's Fair, 1939 and 1964, undated (Drawer 2)
- Series 2: Brooklyn, 1850-2018; 10 Linear Feet in 5 filing cabinet drawers
  - African-Americans -- Black History, undated (Drawer 2)
  - African-Americans -- Abolition, undated (Drawer 2)
  - African-Americans -- Slavery, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Architecture -- General, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Architecture -- Brownstones, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Art and Artists -- General, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Art and Artists -- Authors, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Art and Artists -- William Sidney Mount, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Banks -- General, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Banks -- Brooklyn Savings Bank, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Banks -- East NY Savings Bank, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Banks -- Williamsburg Savings Bank, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Banks -- Dime Savings Bank, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Baseball -- Brooklyn Dodgers, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Baseball -- Brooklyn Dodgers Predecessors, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Bridges -- General, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Bridges -- Brooklyn Bridge, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Bridges -- Brooklyn Bridge Centennial, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- General, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Atlantic Terminal, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Atlantic Yards Project, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Borough Hall, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Brooklyn Historical Society, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Historic Houses, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Lefferts Homestead, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Litchfield Villa, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- MetroTech Center, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Old Stone House, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Pierrepont Office Building, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Williamsburg Savings Bank Building, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Buildings -- Wyckoff-Bennett, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Business and Businesses -- General, undated (Drawer 2)
  - Business and Businesses -- Abraham and Strauss, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Business and Businesses -- Breweries, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Business and Businesses -- Con Edison, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Business and Businesses -- Drugstores, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Business and Businesses -- E. .G. Bowman, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Business and Businesses -- Pfizer, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Cemeteries -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Cemeteries -- Cemetery of the Evergreens, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Cemeteries -- Cypress Hill Abbey, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Cemeteries -- Greenwood Cemetery, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Charities -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Charities -- Brooklyn Bureau of Community Service, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Sunday school/Anniversary Day Parade, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- African Methodist Episcopal/Baptist Churches General, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- African Wesleyan Methodist Episcopal Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- All Saints' Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Bethany Baptist Church of Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Church of the Pilgrims, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Church of the Redeemer, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- First Presbyterian of Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- First Unitarian Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Flatlands Reformed Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Greenpoint Reformed Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Hanson Place Central Methodist Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Lafayette Avenue Presbyterian Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Methodist Episcopal, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Plymouth Church of the Pilgrims, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Reformed Protestant Dutch Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Roman Catholic, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- St. Ann and the Holy Trinity Episcopal Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- St. Francis Xavier Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- St. Teresa of Avila, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- St. Peter and Paul's Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Spencer Memorial Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Churches -- Trinity Church, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Clubs -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Clubs -- American Legion, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Clubs -- Bay Ridge Reading Club, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Clubs -- Crescent Athletic Club, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Clubs -- Masons, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Clubs -- Montauk Club, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Clubs -- Prospect Club, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Clubs -- Upanin Haven Club, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Crime and Law Enforcement, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Department Stores, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- Chinese, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- Dutch, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- Ethnic Bias, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- German, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- German -- Turn Verein Association, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- Hispanic, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- Immigration, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- Italian, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- Japanese, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- Jewish, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Ethnic Groups -- West Indian, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Events -- Anniversaries, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Events -- Festivals, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Events -- Holidays, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Events -- Bicentennial, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Film and Television -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Film and Television -- The Honeymooners, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Firefighting -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Food, Restaurants, Eating -- General, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Food, Restaurants, Eating -- Gage and Tollner, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Food, Restaurants, Eating -- Menus, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Garbage and Waste Management, undated (Drawer 3)
  - Geneology -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Geneology -- Family Histories, undated (Drawer 4)
  - History -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
  - History -- Battle of Long Island, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- Brooklyn Hospital, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- Flushing Hospital, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- Industriaal Home for the Blind, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- Long Island College Hospital, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Health, Hospitals, and Healthcare -- New York Methodist Hospital, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Hotels, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Industries -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Industries -- Ship Building, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Labor -- Labor Disputes/Strikes, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Labor -- Labor Disputes/Strikes -- Boards of Trade, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender (LGBT), undated (Drawer 4)
  - Libraries -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Libraries -- Brooklyn Public Library, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Literature, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Maps -- Ward Maps, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Mayors, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Military, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Monuments and Statues, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Museums -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Museums -- Brooklyn Children's Museum, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Museums -- Brooklyn Museum, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Music -- Songs and Music, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Music -- Anniversary Hymns, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Native Americans, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Navy Yard, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Neighborhoods -- General, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Neighborhoods -- Bay Ridge, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Neighborhoods -- Bedford-Stuyvesant, undated (Drawer 4)
  - Neighborhoods -- Bensonhurst, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Boerum Hill, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Borough Park, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Brighton Beach, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Brooklyn Heights, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Brooklyn Heights Promenade, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Brownsville, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Bushwick, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Canarsie, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Carroll Gardens, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Clinton Hill, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Cobble Hill, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Coney Island, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Crown Heights, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Cypress Hills, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Ditmas Park, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Downtown Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- DUMBO, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Dyker Heights, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- East New York, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Flatbush, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Flatlands, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Fort Greene, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Fort Hamilton, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Fulton Ferry, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Gerritsen Beach Mill, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Gowanus, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Gravesend, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Greenpoint, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Kensington, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Lefferts Garden, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neigh borhoods -- Manhattan Beach, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Marine Park, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Midwood, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Mill Basin, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- New Lots, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Park Slope, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Prospect Heights, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Prospect-Lefferts Gardens, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Prospect Park South, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Red Hook, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Seagate, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Sheepshead Bay, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- South Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 5)
  - Neighborhoods -- Stuyvesant Heights, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Neighborhoods -- Sunset Park, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Neighborhoods -- Vinegar Hill, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Neighborhoods -- Weeksvillle, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Neighborhoods -- Williamsburg, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Neighborhoods -- Windsor Terrace, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Newspapers, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- General, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- American Institute of Architects, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Angel Guardian - Children and Family Services, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- The Arbuckle Institute, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Boy Scouts, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Boys Welfare Foundation, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Education and Cultural Alliance, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Better Brooklyn Committee, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corp., undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Borough Park Historical Society, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Arts and Culture Association, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Bar Association, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Benevolent Society, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Chamber of Commerce, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Historical Society and Long Island Historical Society, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Historical Society and Long Island Historical Society -- Low Family History, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Historical Society and Long Island Historical Society -- Livingston Family History, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Historical Society and Long Island Historical Society -- Events/Programs, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn In Touch, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Red Cross, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Rotary Club, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brooklyn Civil Council, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Brownstone Revival Committee, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- CAMBA, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Downtown Brooklyn Development Association, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Emerald Association of Long Island, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Energy Center, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Fund for the Borough of Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Grow NYC, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Guardian Angels, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Independent Neighborhood Democrats, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Junior League of Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Kings County Historical Society, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Long Island Association, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Neighbors Together Corporation, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- New England Society of Brooklyn, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- New York State Coalition of Concerned Legal Professionals, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Nurses Association of the Counties of Long Island, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Paragon Progressive Community Action, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Plymouth Institute, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Society of Colonial Wars, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Society of Old Brooklynites, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- United Merchants of 5th Avenue, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- Visiting Nurse Association, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Organizations, Institutions, Associations, Societies -- 28th Ward Taxpayers Protective Association, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Parks -- General, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Parks -- Brooklyn Botanic Garden, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Parks -- Brookyn Bridge Park, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Parks -- Fort Greene Park, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Parks -- Grand Army Plaza, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Parks -- Jones Beach, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Parks -- Prospect Park, undated (Drawer 6)